-CAYDEN WELTER ---

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY STUDENT

CONTACT



608-573-1187



□ caydenwelter@gmail.com



LinkedIn



caydenwelter.com

ABOUT ME

I am currently a Data Science & Computer Science student attending UW-Madison. I am planning to major in Data Science and obtain a certificate in Computer Science and expect to graduate in May of 2024. I have experience with help desk, endpoint management & patching, scripting, hardware deployment, asset management, and Windows. I have good knowledge of many programming and scripting languages. I have a strong knowledge of Microsoft products including Outlook, am comfortable with fast-paced environments, and enjoy working in teams. I have a lot of customer service experience and consider myself to be a "people person". In my free time, I enjoy working on personal projects and riding my motorcycle.

SKILLS

- Java & C#
- Python
- PowerShell
- Linux/Unix/Bash
- Windows 10/11
- Microsoft Office Products
- Communication & Customer Service
- Ticketing Systems, Such as Zendesk
- Atlassian Products (Jira & Confluence)
- Endpoint Management/Patching/PCI
- Some System Administration

2022-2024 (expected) | GPA: 3.76

certificate in Computer Science.

I am majoring in Data Science with a

EXPERIENCE

Information Technology Intern at *University of Wisconsin Foundation*

2022-Present

Responsibilities include handing help desk tickets, deploying hardware and software, assisting in onboarding in teammates, assisting with daily operations, solving hardware & software problems of various degrees, and completing projects as assigned. Projects have included developing VBA scripts to automatically audit our asset inventory and developing PowerShell scripts to automate workflows.

Retail Salesworker at Kwik Trip

2020-2022

Responsibilities included providing excellent customer service and preparing food in the kitchen in a safe yet efficient manner.

Shift Lead/Keyholder at Ace Hardware DeForest

2019-2020

Responsibilities included opening and closing the store, solving customer complaints in a professional manner, and completing routine duties as assigned.

Madison Area Technical College

2020-2022 | GPA: 3.92

EDUCATION

UW - Madison

I spent the first 2 years of my bachelor's degree at MATC and transferred the credits to UW-Madison

Account Representative at WP Beverages Pepsi-Cola 2019-2019

Responsibilities included ensuring that the stock level of Pepsi and Wis-Pak products were full in stores across the greater Madison Area.